



I have already finished some projects using C languages in my studies and now I am learning how to develop the websites properly (JS, HTML, CSS). Two months ago I have come to realize that programming is a place where I can see myself in the next 5 years. I want to dive deeper into this world and that is why I am looking for my first experiences and new challenges.

Personal Info



+48 662096409



Statkprivate@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/mateusz S-statkiewicz



https://github.com/Keitar6/Ke itar6.github.io.git

Education

2016-10

Automatic Control and Robotics, Bachelor of Engineering

- 2020-02

University of Science and Technology in Wroclaw, Polska

2020-10

Mechanics, Master degree - present

University of Science and Technology in Wrocław, Wrocław, Polska

Skills

JavaScript, HTML, CSS Basic knowledge of C, Github and Vs code

Soft skills:

- Hardworking
- Out of the box thinking.
- Ability to work in a team.
- Organization of own work.
- Time management
- Communicativeness and openness.

Work History

2018-02 - 2018-10 Science club software / embedded engineer

Science club "Robocik", Wrocław, Polska

Creation of autonomous submarines and ROVs.

Junior mechanical design engineer

- Rebuilding the communication system in the prototype ROV
- Working in a team of 4 people
- Programming with C language

2022-03

- 2022-05 Seamore, Wrocław, Polska

- · Creation of a optical fiber winder

• Development of a ROVs construction

- · Working in a team of 6 people
- Preparations of 3D and 2D documentation

Languages

- 2022-03

2021-02 English language - B2

German language During studying ~A1

Hobby

- Diving into the programming world
- 3D printing technology
- Drama and fantasy series
- Tennis

Junior design engineer

NG Engineering, Wrocław, Polska

- Realisations of a projects for leading companys from the automotive industry in a team of 2 to 4
- Feasibility analysis in terms of injection mold technology
- Working in CatiaV5 mainly in generative design and solid module